business-ethics.com 2011-05-26

# Business Ethics | Business Ethics Privacy Policy

At _Business Ethics_ Magazine (www.business-ethics.com, or the “Site”), we appreciate your readership and value your personal privacy. We respect the personal nature of the information you provide us on the Site and acknowledge the importance of protecting this information. _Business Ethics_ Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you use the Site and services.  Please read this statement carefully before proceeding to access Business-ethics.com.  Your use of the Site indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect. The policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our policy.

**Information We Gather**

The information we gather falls into two categories: 1) personal information, i.e. your name and email address, which you voluntarily supply when you subscribe to the Site or its newsletter or 2) personal information, i.e. your name, email address, and website, which you provide when posting a comment on the Site.  _Business Ethics_ Magazine and its owner New Mountain Media LLC (“NMM”) are the sole owners of the information collected on the Site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Use of Information**

_Business Ethics Magazine_ may use information collected to improve the Site and services.

If you have registered online as a subscriber or to post comments, we will not sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your e-mail address without your permission. This also applies to any information that personally identifies you, except as noted immediately below.  However, your personal information may be shared with a court, law enforcement or government agency under the circumstances detailed in the Terms of Use.

We may send you information related to the Site. The information collected from you may be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services. Users who choose to subscribe to the mailing list will receive regular emails from the Site in the form of content from the Site or newsletters.  If you do not wish to receive emails, please do not subscribe to the Service.

**Links**

The Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that NMM and _Business Ethics_ are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by NMM and _Business Ethics_.

**Security Statement**

_Business Ethics_ takes the following types of security measures: use of technologies and policies such as limited access data-centers, firewall technology, and password protection.

While we implement the above security measures on this site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.

**How To Contact Us**

For any questions or comments regarding our information or security practices, you may contact us by e-mail at privacy@business-ethics.com or by mail at Business Ethics Magazine, New Mountain Media LLC, 55 West 39th Street, Suite 800, New York, NY 10018.
